- A thoroughly wonderful show
from the world-famous Dancing Crooners.
Next, ladies and gentlemen,
we have three fine young men from Seattle.
(crowd cheering)
They're coming. Hold on, they're coming.
They're thoroughly all
right and decent fellows
with their hit single "In Bloom."
Here they are, Nirvana.
(crowd cheering)
(heavy grunge music)
♪ Sell the kids for food ♪
♪ Weather changes moods ♪
♪ Spring is here again ♪
♪ Reproductive glands ♪
♪ He's the one ♪
♪ Who likes all our pretty songs ♪
♪ And he likes to sing along ♪
♪ And he likes to shoot his gun ♪
♪ But he knows not what it means ♪
♪ Knows not what it means ♪
♪ And I say he's the one ♪
♪ Who likes all our pretty songs ♪
♪ And he likes to sing along ♪
♪ And he likes to shoot his gun ♪
♪ But he knows not what it means ♪
♪ Knows not what it means ♪
♪ And I say yeah ♪
♪ We can have some more ♪
♪ Nature is a whore ♪
♪ Bruises on the fruit ♪
♪ Tender age in bloom ♪
♪ He's the one ♪
♪ Who likes all our pretty songs ♪
♪ And he likes to sing along ♪
♪ And he likes to shoot his gun ♪
♪ But he knows not what it means ♪
♪ Knows not what it means ♪
♪ And I say he's the one ♪
♪ Who likes all our pretty songs ♪
♪ And he likes to sing along ♪
♪ And he likes to shoot his gun ♪
♪ But he knows not what it means ♪
♪ Knows not what it means ♪
♪ And I say yeah ♪
♪ He's the one ♪
♪ Who likes all our pretty songs ♪
♪ And he likes to sing along ♪
♪ And he likes to shoot his gun ♪
♪ But he knows not what it means ♪
♪ Knows not what it means ♪
♪ And I say he's the one ♪
♪ Who likes all our pretty songs ♪
♪ And he likes to sing along ♪
♪ And he likes to shoot his gun ♪
♪ But he knows not what it means ♪
♪ Knows not what it means ♪
♪ And I say yeah ♪
(crowd cheering)
- All right, everybody, let's hear it
for these three nice,
decent, clean-cut young men.
I really can't say enough
nice things about them.
They're gonna be really big stars.
Let's give a big hand to Nirvana.
(crowd cheering)